winner.com 2013-05-22

# Privacy Policy

### Winner Sport Respects Your Privacy

### 

The following statements detail the information gathered by Winner Sport.

### ACCOUNT CREATION PROCESS

###   
 **Information collected**

We collect personal information from visitors to this website through the use of online forms and every time you e-mail us your details. We also collect information about the transactions you undertake including details of payment cards used. The personal information that we collect may include your name, email address, home address, telephone number, debit/credit card data and date of birth and other information collected on registration or through surveys which we, or undertakings engaged by us for such purpose, shall undertake.

### USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

###   
 **We process your personal information for the purposes of:**

(a) creating and managing player accounts and records;  
(b) administering player accounts;  
(c) providing and personalising our services;  
(d) dealing with your inquiries and requests;  
(e) notifying you about updates to our software and/or services;  
(f) ensuring we are able to fulfill our regulatory responsibilities by verifying the accuracy of any information you give us;  
(g) our general regulatory compliance, crime prevention and prosecution of offenders including, where appropriate, dealing with requests for information by authorised entities for the sharing of information;  
(h) carrying out market research campaigns;  
(i) providing you with information about and support for products and services;  
(j) marketing our services or products or those of other entities within our group of companies; and  
(k) supporting any of the intended purposes specifically stated at the time at which you provided the personal information.  
These are the “Purposes” for which we may collect personal data.  
If you do NOT want to receive any e-mail from us, please send us a blank e-mail with the word "remove" in the subject to sports@winner.com.

### DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

 **We may, for the Purposes, disclose your personal information to any of the following recipients (“Recipients”):**

(i) any companies within our group and to their employees who have a need to know such information;  
(ii) any third parties which provide services to us in order to allow or enable us to provide you with gaming services, including by way of example payment processors and data verifiers;  
(iii) any third parties who provide services to us in relation to the operation of Winner Sport;  
(iv) any auditors, contractors or other advisers auditing any of our business processes or who have the need to access such information for the purpose of advising us;  
(v) any regulatory body or authorized entity who may have any reasonable requirement to access such personal information; and  
(vi) any potential purchasers of the Winner Sport business or any investors in it or in any company within our group.

### WEBSITE AND ADVERTISING SYSTEM

As part of the website's operation and for our own statistical analysis of site traffic, our website automatically logs Internet IP addresses. We do NOT log any e-mail address of website visitors.

Our advertising system logs IP addresses to supply more accurate advertising features, such as language-specific banners.

### MAIL POLICY

We do not tolerate spam.   
We received your consent for communication via email.   
We send you promotional emails and updates until such time as you inform us that you do not wish to continue to receive them. 

**You may notify us of your wish to unsubscribe at any time by:**

• Click on the unsubscribe link shown in all http://sports.winner.com email offers and follow the instructions.   
• Call us, Toll Free - UK:+ 0808-1203-498  
• online chat available   
• email us at: sports@winner.com

On receiving your notice, we will immediately stop sending you such e-mails and updates. 

If you continue to receive from us promotional e-mails and updates or any other unsolicited communication after you have asked us to unsubscribe, please report to us at sports@winner.com

### WINNINGS

Your winnings and cash-outs are kept strictly confidential, and winnings information is stored in secure operating environments. Winner Sport does not provide winnings information to any third party unless such information is required to be disclosed by law, regulation or a similar governmental authority.

### SECURITY

Winner Sport uses a number of methods to ensure that all customer information remains confidential. Transferred information is sent using advanced encryption methods and, once stored in our servers, is protected by the most up-to-date firewall technology available to protect data from being misused and/or lost.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding data privacy and security please contact our Customer Support team 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.

### WINNER SPORT IS SSL SECURE

Winner Sport is protected by the best and strongest security available. Our SSL (Secured Socket Layer) utilizes 256-bit encryption. This technology encrypts all personal data transferred between you and Winner Sport. Winner Sport works hard to ensure a safe and secure gaming environment.
